#### Contact

shubhobera98@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shubho09 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Adobe Premiere Pro Video Editing Web Development

## Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
Bengali (Professional Working)

### Certifications

C++ Programming
IBM Blockchain Foundation
Developer V2
Blockchain Basics
Responsive Web Design
Python Basics and Fundamentals

# Shubhojeet Bera

Front-End Developer | Video Editor (Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effects) | Blockchain Enthusiast.

Durg

## Summary

Hey! I'm an Editor | Programmer | Blockchain enthusiast.

Worked as an editor with one of the top educators.

Have over 2.5+ years of experience in Content Creation, had over 60k+ Followers (Youtube + Instagram).

Rather than editing videos, I'm a productive programmer who just loves new technology. Very much interested in Blockchain, Crypto, Defi, DApps, DAOs, NFTs, and more.

For more: https://linktr.ee/shubho09

## Experience

### YouTube

Video Editor at Ashish Futtan Vlogs January 2022 - April 2022 (4 months)

- Working with a Youtube-Vlogger, editing and managing their channel. Helping them to grow immensely.
- Till now edited over 50+ vlogs for their channel.

Unacademy GATE & ESE
Video Editor at Engineering OGs
January 2021 - October 2021 (10 months)

- Working with one of the leading educators of this platform.
- Editing strategic content for aspirants of GATE/ESE (specifically).
- Edited over 40+ videos on their channel (includes Topper Interviews, Strategy to crack GATE/ESE & Podcasts).

# Education

Shri Shankaracharya Technical Campus

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology · (2020 - 2024)

Khalsa Public Higher Secondary School Science · (2007 - 2020)